Guide to the Western Pennsylvania Conservancy Records and Photographs, 1885-2006 AIS.1999.13
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs, 1885-2006; 1950-2004; II.
  - Land and Water, 1885-1975; 1950-1975; 1.
    - Laurel Ridge State Park, Prints and Negatives (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Little Beaver, Prints (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Lone Star Farm, Prints (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Loyalhanna Gorge, Prints (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Markleysburg Bog, Prints (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - McConnell's Mill State Park, Prints and Negatives (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - McConnell's Mill State Park, Prints and Negatives (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - McConnell's Mill State Park Summer Outing, July 30, 1960; Prints and Negatives (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - McCoy Farm Views, Whitney Creek, Prints (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Meadow Run, Prints (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Mercer Bog, Prints (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Miller Esker, Prints (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Moraine State Park, Prints and Negatives (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Moraine State Park, Slides (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Mount Davis Natural Area, Prints (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Mountain Streams, Prints and Negatives (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Muddy Creek, Prints (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Octagonal Schoolhouse, Butler County, Prints (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Ohiopyle Copy Artwork and Maps, Prints and Negatives (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Ohiopyle Falls, Prints and Negatives (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Ohiopyle Historical, Prints (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Ohiopyle Region, Prints (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Ohiopyle Region, Slides (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Ohiopyle Region and Ohiopyle State Park, Prints and Negatives (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Ohiopyle Region, Prints (Box 42, Folder 1-21)
      19 mounted prints of the Ohiopyle Region, taken between 1885 and 1890. Prints of various areas throughout the Ohiopyle region are depicted, including: Cucumber Falls; Meadow Run; Lovers Leap; Ohiopyle Falls; and the B&O train station at Ohiopyle. 5 of the 19 prints depict Daisy Kinzer and George M. Kinzer at various areas in the Ohiopyle region. 1 print depicting the old covered bridge at Ohiopyle. 1 print depicting a woman standing on the National Highway east of Uniontown, taken in the early 1900s.
    - Ohiopyle Region, Glass Plate Negatives (Box 43, Folder 1-14)
      12 glass plate negatives taken about 1902 by photographer Frank M. Hull. 9 glass plate negatives depict the Ohiopyle region, including: Cucumber Falls; Ohiopyle Falls; and the Youghiogheny River. 3 glass plate negatives depict the lower Allegheny from Monument Hill. 1 lantern slide taken about 1910 by Dr. O.E. Jennings, depicting the Ohiopyle Falls. 1 print of Cucumber Falls enclosed in leather-bound book.
    - Oil Creek Valley, Prints and Negatives (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Old Allegheny, Prints and Negatives (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Old Stone House, Prints and Negatives (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Old Stone House, Prints and Negatives (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Old Stone House Copy Artwork, Prints and Negatives (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Old Stone House Picture Postcards, Prints (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Otter Creek, Prints (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania State Parks, Prints (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Pine Creek Gorge, Prints (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Pine Swamp, Prints (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Pithole, Prints (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh, Prints (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh Parks and Playgrounds, Prints (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Poland Municipal Forest, Prints (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Poorbaugh Property, Prints and Negatives (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - President Oil, Prints (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - President Oil, Slides (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Presque Isle State Park, Prints (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Presque Isle State Park, Slides (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Prince Gallitzin State Park, Prints (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Pymatuning Reservoir State Park, Prints (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Quakertown Falls, Prints (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Raccoon Creek State Park, Prints (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Raystown Macrosite, Rosecrans Bog, Slides (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Renfrew Woods, Prints (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Scenic Views, Prints and Negatives (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Scenic, Summer, Sunsets, Slides (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Scholard's Run, Prints and Negatives (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Shawnee State Park, Prints (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Sideling Hill Creek, Slides (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Sinking Valley, Slides (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Snyder Property, Prints (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Springfield Falls, Prints (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Storm Damage, Prints (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - Streams, Prints and Negatives (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - Strip Mines, Prints and Negatives (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - Sugarloaf, Prints (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - Sugar Run, Prints (Box 44, Folder 38)
    - Susquehanna River, Prints and Negatives (Box 44, Folder 39)
    - Tharp Knob, Prints (Box 44, Folder 40)
    - Titus Bog, Prints (Box 44, Folder 41)
    - Todd Sanctuary, Prints (Box 44, Folder 42)
    - Twelve Mile Island, Prints (Box 44, Folder 43)
    - Trees, Prints and Negatives (Box 44, Folder 44)
    - Tree Planting, Prints (Box 44, Folder 45)
    - Tytoona Cave Natural Area, Prints and Negatives (Box 44, Folder 46)
    - USX Property, Erie County, Prints and Negatives (Box 44, Folder 47)
    - Wake Robin Reserve, Prints (Box 44, Folder 48)
    - Washington Crossing State Park, Prints (Box 44, Folder 49)
    - Water, Waterfalls, Winter, Slides (Box 44, Folder 50)
    - Wattsburg Bog, Prints (Box 44, Folder 51)
    - Wattsburg Bog, Slides (Box 44, Folder 52)
    - Whann Run, Prints (Box 44, Folder 53)
    - Western Maryland Railway Copy Artwork, Prints (Box 44, Folder 54)
    - Wildflower Reserve, Prints and Negatives (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Wildflower Reserve, Prints (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Wildflower Reserve, Braun Shelter, Prints (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Wildflower Reserve, Slides (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Wildlife, Prints (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Wildlife, Slides (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Willis Creek Confluence with Brush Creek, Prints (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Wilroy Furnace, Prints (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Wolf Creek, Slides (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Youghiogheny River and Dam, Prints (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Oversize Prints, Prints (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
  - Community Garden Program, 1975-2006; 1988-2004; 2.
    The WPC works with community organizations in Western Pennsylvania to plant and maintain gardens found along roadways, neighborhoods, and businesses. This subseries contains prints, negatives, and 35mm slides depicting roadways, tunnels, bridges, schools, and communities throughout Western Pennsylvania. Boxes 53-61 contain print packs, which include prints, negatives, 35mm slides and CDs. Furthermore, their description is preceeded by an alphabetical/chronological numbering scheme, which is found on each print pack. The numbering scheme seems to have been put in place to locate items that were separated, but the system is not used consistently until the year 2002, with quite a few gaps in between.
    - Airport Busway; Allderdice High School; Allegheny River Boulevard and Washington Boulevard; Alloy Oxygen; Amanda Street and Charles Street; Anderson Street Bridge; Arbor Day; Arlington Avenue and McArdle Avenue; Aviary Recap, Slides (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Banksville Elementary School; Barry Street and Josephine Avenue; Beaver County and Beaver Valley Mall; Beechwood Boulevard and Reynolds Street; Beechwood Elementary School; Belmar Elementary School; Birmingham Bridge; Bloomfield; Bon Air Elementary School; Brentwood Middle School and High School; Bridgeville, Pa., Slides (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Brighton Road and Charles Street; Brookline Elementary School; Brooklyn Botanical Gardens; Brownsville, Pa.; Burgwin Elementary School; Butler County (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - California Avenue and Termon Avenue; Canal Street; Carmalt Middle School; Carnegie Mansfield; Carrick Volunteer Fire Department; Carson Street and Sarah Street; Castle Shannon Boulevard, Slides (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Centre Avenue and Herron Avenue, Slides (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Chartiers Elementary School; Chatham Elementary School; Chestnut Street; Chicago Botanical Gardens, Slides (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Clairton, Pa.; Clarion, Pa.; Claysville Welcome Center; Clayton Elementary School; Clapville, Pa., Slides (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Colerain Street and Route 51; Colfax Elementary School; Columbus Middle School; Concord Elementary School; Conroy Elementary School; Connellsville, Pa., Slides (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Court Place; Crawford Avenue and Centre Avenue; Crescent Elementary School; Crumb Rubber Project, Slides (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Demo Gardens and Community Vegetable Gardens; Donora, Pa.; Dormont Avenue and Banksville Road; Downtown Greening; Downtown Hanging Baskets, Slides (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - East Hills Elementary School; East Liberty; East Park; Edgewood, Pa.; Erie, Pa.; Etna, Pa., Slides (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Faith Gallow Garden; First Unitarian Church; Fifth Avenue; 55th Street and Butler Street; Forbes Avenue and South Dallas Avenue, Slides (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Fort Pitt Elementary School; Fort Pitt Tunnels, Slides (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Fort Pitt Tunnels, Slides (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - 40th Street Bridge; 48th Street and Butler Street; Frankstown Avenue and Bennett Street; Franklin, Pa.; Friendship Academy; Fulton School, Slides (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Gateway High School; General Robinson Street; Gettysburg, Pa.; Gladstone Middle School; Grant Street; Greeley Avenue and Josephine Avenue; Greenfield, Pa., Slides (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Greenfield Elementary School; Greengate Road; Greentree West; Grove City, Slides (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Harrisburg State Street Bridge; Haymaker, Haymaker Extension, Haymaker Road and Route 48; Hays Flood Damage, Hays Route 885 and Glass Run Road; Hazelwood Avenue, Beechwood Boulevard and Saline Street; Highland Park Bridge; Hill District Police Station, Slides (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Homer Street and Walz Avenue; Homestead High Level Bridge; Homewood Montessori School; Hope Hollow Road; Hollidaysburg, Pa., Slides (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Housing Authority, City of Pittsburgh, Senior Citizen High Rises, Slides (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Indiana, Pa.; Ivory Avenue and Evergreen Road; Johnston Elementary School; Johnstown, Pa., Slides (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Kennedy Township, Pine Hollow Road and Heckle Road; Kirby Welcome Center; Kirkpatrick Street and Fifth Avenue; Knoxville Elementary and Middle School; Knox Avenue and Brownsville Road, Slides (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Langley High School; Lemington Elementary School; Letsche Education Center; Liberty Tunnel; Ligonier Route 30 and Route 711, Slides (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Lincoln Avenue and Frankstown Avenue; Lincoln Elementary School; Linden Circle, Linden Elementary School, Linden Avenue and McPherson Boulevard, Linden Avenue and Simonton Street, Linden Avenue and Thomas Boulevard, Slides (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Light Rail Transit Station; Longwood Gardens; Lydia Street, Lydia Street and Chestnut Street, Slides (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Manchester Township; Mansfield Avenue and Campbells Run Road; Marshall Avenue and California Avenue; Martin Luther King, Jr. Elementary School; McCleary Elementary School, Slides (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - McIntyre Road and McKnight Road; McKees Rocks Bridge; McKelvy Elementary School, Slides (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Meadville City Hall, Meadville Gateway, Meadville 2nd School District, Meadville Triangle; Mellon Bank, Slides (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Mifflin School; Miller Elementary School; Miryam's Women's Shelter, Slides (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Millvale, Pa.; Minadeo Elementary School; Monessen, Tyrol Boulevard and Route 906; Monroeville, Pa.; Moon/Clinton Interchange, Moon Township, Slides (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Morningside Elementary School; Morrowfield Avenue, Tilbury Street and Beechwood Boulevard; Mosside Elementary School, Slides (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - National Botanical Gardens; New Bethlehem, Pa.; New Kensington, Pa.; Noblestown Road and Durbin Street, Slides (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - North Avenue and Brighton Road; North Braddock Avenue and Penn Avenue; Northside Police Station; Northview Heights School and Day Care, Slides (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Oakmont, Pa.; Oil City; Oliver High School; O'Neil Boulevard and Hartman Street; Overbrook Elementary School, Slides (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Parkway West; Parnassus Triangle; Peabody High School; Penn Avenue and Friendship Avenue; East Pennsboro, Route 11 and Route 15; Perry Traditional Academy; Perrysville Avenue and Federal Street; Philips Elementary School; Phipps Conservatory and Botanical Gardens, Slides (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Pittsburgh Project; Pizza Site, Knox Avenue and Brownsville Road; Point State Park; Point Breeze; Polish Hill; Prestige Bank; Prince of Peace School; Prospect Middle School, Slides (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Quinten Roosevelt Elementary School; Rankin Bridge; Regent Square School; Reizenstein School; Riverfront Trail at Robotics; Riverview Park; Rochester, Pa.; Rooney Middle School, Slides (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Saxonburg Road and Route 970; Sarah Heinz House; Schaffer Elementary School; Schenley Park Plaza; Science Center; Scott/Carnegie Interchange; 2nd Avenue and Hazelwood Avenue; Shady Lane School, Slides (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Shaler Intermediate School; Sheraden Elementary School; Slippery Rock; Small Grants; South Aiken Avenue and Centre Avenue; South Dallas Avenue and Wilkins Avenue; South Hills Middle School; Southside Market House; South Park, Slides (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Spring Garden; Spring Hill Elementary School; Squirrel Hill Tunnel; State College; Stephen Foster; Sterrett Classical Academy; Steuben Street and Middletown Road; Sunoco; Swissvale, Pa., Slides (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Tamaqua, Pa.; Terrace Street and Darragh Street; Tri-Boro Expressway; Tyrone, Pa.; Uniontown, Pa.; Van Braam; Venture Street, Slides (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Washington Polytechnic Academy; Waynesburg, Pa.; Weigle Hill Road and Route 48; Weil Elementary School; West Deer; West End; West Liberty Academy; West Side Elementary School, Slides (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Westinghouse High School; Westwood Elementary School; White Oak; Wilkins Township; Wylie Avenue and Elmore Street, Slides (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - WPC Building Planters; Wildflowers; Xeriscape, Slides (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - 11th Street and Carson Street; 12th Street and Carson Street; 12th Street and Sarah Street; 22/30/60 Interchange; 48th Street and Butler Street; 1835 Forbes Avenue; 3400 Butler Street; 5700 Butler Street, Slides (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Arbor Day and Philadelphia Tour, 1986; Prints and Negatives (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Botanical Garden Site Visit, Prints and Negatives (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - California Avenue, 1985-1986; Negatives and Slides (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Carmalt School, About 1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Community Gardens, 1980; Prints (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Community Gardens, 1986; Prints and Negatives (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Community Gardens: Allentown, Brighton Heights, and Broadhead Manor, 1980-1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Community Gardens: Charles Street, Cove Place, East Allegheny, East Ohio Street, and Elliott, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Community Gardens: Father Fred's, Frick Park, Garfield, Hazelwood, and Hill District, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Community Gardens: Homewood, Larimer and Carmier, Northside, Point Breeze, Polish Hill, Schenley Heights, South Oakland, and Stanton Heights, 1980-1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Community Gardens and Site Specs, 1980-1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Deutschtown Garden Site, Prints (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Drain Property, Prints (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Duquesne Slag, 1986; Prints and Negatives (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Floral Beds: West End and Stephen Foster, 1985-1986; Prints and Negatives (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Gardens and Park Floral Displays, 1982; Prints (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Garden Pictures Used for Display, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Gardens and Planting Activities, Prints (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Garden Shots, 1980; Prints (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Garden Shots, 1982; Prints (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Garden Shots, 1984; Prints (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Garden Shots, 1987; Prints and Negatives (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Garden Shots, 1988; Prints (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Garden Shots, 1980-1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Garden Shots, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Garden Shots, 1980-1989; Negatives (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Garden Tomato Patch, 1985; Prints and Negatives (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Garfield YMCA, 1986; Prints and Negatives (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Hanging Baskets, Prints (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Hillel Street, 1986; Prints and Negatives (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Housing Authority, City of Pittsburgh, Senior Citizen High Rise Floral Beds, 1986; Prints and Negatives (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Limbach/NCA, 1986; Prints and Negatives (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Lord Corporation and Keystone Fund PA-DCN, Prints and Negatives (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Market Square Flowers and Molly's Trolley, Prints and Negatives (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - North Canal Street, 1985; Prints and Negatives (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - North Side Post Office, 1986; Prints and Negatives (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - New Gardens, 1981; Prints (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Old Gardens, 1981; Prints (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Parklets, 1981; Prints (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Parklets, 1975-1985; Prints (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Picture Boards, 1993; Negatives (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh Park and Playground Fund, 1979-1980; Prints (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh Park and Playground Fund, 1980; Prints and Slides (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh Park and Playground Fund, 1981; Prints (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh Park and Playground Fund, 1985; Prints and Negatives (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Pittsburgh Park and Playground Fund, 1985; Slides (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Playgrounds, 1975-1985; Prints (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Site Specs, 1975-1985; Prints (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Southside Festival, Between 1978 and 1982; Prints (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Whales Tail, 1986; Prints and Negatives (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - 1. Housing Authority, City of Pittsburgh, Senior Citizen High Rise Floral Beds, 1987; Prints (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - 2. Housing Authority, City of Pittsburgh, Senior Citizen High Rise Floral Beds, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - 3. Housing Authority, City of Pittsburgh, Senior Citizen High Rise Floral Beds, 1984-1985 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - 4. Housing Authority, City of Pittsburgh, Senior Citizen High Rise Floral Beds, 1986; Prints (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - 5. Housing Authority, City of Pittsburgh, Senior Citizen High Rise Floral Beds, 1980-1987; Prints (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - 6. Housing Authority, City of Pittsburgh, Senior Citizen High Rise Floral Beds, 1980-1987; Prints (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - 7. Housing Authority, City of Pittsburgh, Senior Citizen High Rise Floral Beds: Addison Towers, East Hills, Garfield, Kelly Street, Bidwiel, and Pressly Street, 1980-1987 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - 8. Carrick Regency Senior Citizen High Rise Floral Beds, 1980-1987; Prints (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - 1. Alcosan; Bethany House Clean-up; and CCAC West Mifflin, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - 2. East Liberty; and North Avenue and Brighton Road, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - 3. Graphics, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - 4. Great Tomato Patch, 1985; Prints (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - 5. Greenways, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - 6. Hazelwood Avenue and 2nd Avenue; and Philadelphia Conference, 1980-1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - 7. Highland Park Main Entrance, 1984; Prints (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - 8. Highland Park Reservoir, 1980-1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - 9. Hill District Police Station, 1988; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - 10. Linden Avenue and Thomas Boulevard, and Linden Avenue and McPherson Boulevard, 1983-1985; Prints (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - 11. Market Square, 1984; Prints (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - 12. McKees Rocks Bridge, 1988; Prints (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - 13. McKees Rocks, 1988; Prints (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - 14. North Side Police Station, 1984; Prints (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - 15. People, 1980-1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - 16. Downtown; Stanwick Street; Troy Hill; and Lowrie Street, Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - 17. Pittsburgh Airport, Hampton Inn; and Duquesne Slag, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - 18. Soldiers and Sailors, 1988; Prints (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - 19. Spring Garden, 1988; Prints (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - 20. Stadium Area, 1980-1989; Negatives (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - 21. Stadium; and Perry Point, 1980-1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - 22. Sunflowers at Westinghouse Building, Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - 23. Stadium Area and Sunflowers at Westinghouse Building, 1980-1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - 24. Stephen Foster, 1985-1988; Prints (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - 25. Stephen Foster; Schenley Park Plaza; and Buena Vista Street, 1987; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - 26. Thomas Boulevard, Point Breeze, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - 27. Troy Hill, 1988; Prints (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - 28. Troy Hill, 1988; Prints (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - 30. West Park Circle, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - 31. Mrs. Hagler and Rick; Buena Vista Street; Melrose; and Sherman Street, 1980-1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - 32. Tripoli Street; Madison Avenue Garden; Buena Vista Street; Sherman Street; Liverpool Gardens; Manchester Community Garden; Arch and Sherman Community Garden; and Warlo Street, 1985-1986; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - 33. Greenfield; Johnathan Court; Kelly Street; and Melrose, 1980-1989; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - 34. California Avenue, 1984; Prints (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - 35. California Avenue and Kirkland Street, 1987; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - 36. Perrysville Fire Station; and California Avenue, 1986; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - 37. Fineview Park, North Side, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - 38. Homewood Cemetery Community Garden, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - 39. House of Crossroads, Grove Street Community Garden, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - 40. Manhattan and Paige Streets, Manchester, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 48)
    - 41. Meadow Street Community Garden, 1990; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 49)
    - 42. Mexican War Street Community Garden, Annual Garden Tour, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 50)
    - 43. Perrysville Avenue; and Perry Hilltop, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 51)
    - 44. Riverview Manor, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 52)
    - 45. Rose and Dinwiddie Streets, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 53)
    - 46. Spring Garden, Church Citizen Planting, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 54)
    - 47. Formosa Street Playground; Allegheny Cemetery Community Garden; and Success Street Playground, 1985-1987; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 55)
    - 48. Michigan Street Flower Beds; Ball Seed Co.; and Chicago Botanical Gardens, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 56)
    - 49. Longwood Gardens, Philadelphia, 1980-1989; Prints (Box 53, Folder 57)
    - 50. Vancouver, Canada, 1987; Prints and Negatives (Box 53, Folder 58)